[Music]
[음악]
our live recording is a trusted ally to
우리의 라이브 녹음은
solid-state drives by Kingston
Kingston의 솔리드 스테이트 드라이브
technology revive your computer with
기술로 컴퓨터를 부활 시키십시오
improved performance and reliability
성능 및 신뢰성 향상
over traditional hard drives with
기존 하드 드라이브보다
Kingston SSDs category 5 TV streams live
Kingston SSD 카테고리 5 TV 스트림 라이브
with Telestream wire cast and nimble
Telestream 와이어 캐스트 및 민첩한
streamer tune in every week on roku cody
roku cody에서 매주 스 트리머 튜닝
and other HLS video players for local
지역의 다른 HLS 비디오 플레이어
show times visit category 5 TV welcome
쇼 시간 방문 카테고리 5 TV 환영
to the show everybody this is episode
쇼 모두에게 에피소드입니다
number 634 and category 5 is on the air
번호 634와 카테고리 5가 방송 중입니다
this week we've got a great show planned
이번 주에 멋진 공연을 계획했습니다
for you I say that every time but it's
당신을 위해 나는 매번 말하지만 그것은
true we are going to be looking at the
사실 우리는
brand new echo device from Amazon so you
아마존의 새로운 에코 장치로
want to stick around for that and in the
그 주위에 붙어 싶어
meantime you - nice to see you it's
그동안 당신을 만나서 반갑습니다
great to have you here Jeff and Sasha
제프와 사샤
are over there I'm Robby Ferguson and
저기 나는 로비 퍼거슨이고
nice to have you joining us this week
이번 주에 우리와 함께하게되어 반갑습니다
before we get into the show I want to
공연을 시작하기 전에
remind you make sure you subscribe to us
당신이 우리를 구독해야합니다
on YouTube and make sure you click that
YouTube에서 클릭해야합니다.
bell that's going to ensure that you get
당신이 얻을 수 있도록 벨
our notifications every time that we are
우리가있을 때마다 알림
live or when we post brand new videos as
라이브 또는 새로운 동영상을 게시 할 때
well Jeff you remember back in the day
잘 제프 당신은 하루에 다시 기억
when we were just we lads I do and there
우리가 단지 우리 젊은이 였을 때
was a particular game I'm just gonna
내가 할 특정 게임이었습니다
reach over here because I actually have
실제로 가지고 있기 때문에 여기에 도달
it Jeff does this bring back any
제프는 이걸
memories for you oh my gosh yes can you
너를위한 추억 oh my gosh yes can you
believe it has been 20 years 20 years
20 년 20 년이라고 믿어
that's about right since Unreal
언리얼 이후로
Tournament which we now call goty or
우리가 지금 goty라고 부르는 토너먼트
game of the year edition was released
올해의 게임 판이 출시되었습니다
and this is the the actual disc so you
이게 실제 디스크이므로
can still get these on Amazon you'll get
여전히 아마존에서 얻을 수 있습니다.
them used
그들은 사용했다
it's only a couple bucks you can also
그것은 당신이 할 수있는 몇 달러입니다
get the game on Steam for 11 bucks and
11 달러에 Steam에서 게임을 시작하고
you can play Unreal Tournament now this
언리얼 토너먼트를 할 수 있습니다
game I mean for a lot of us holds a lot
게임은 우리를 위해 많은 것을 의미합니다
of nostalgia oh yeah but 20 years and
향수의 오 예하지만 20 년
it's still absolutely playable it's
그것은 여전히 ​​절대적으로 재생 가능합니다.
still a lot of fun this was the original
아직도 많은 재미 이것은 원래였다
I would say Jeff this was the original
나는 Jeff가 이것이 원래라고 말할 것이다.
deathmatch yeah absolutely I mean it was
데스 매치 그래 절대적으로
out around the same time as like I'm
나처럼 같은 시간에
like Commander Keen yeah but I mean as
사령관 킨처럼
far as a first-person shooter it was
1 인칭 슈터 인 한
that you had Team Fortress
팀 포트리스가
counter-strike they were all kind of
그들은 모든 종류의 반격
within the same timeframe of years but
몇 년 동안 같은 기간 내에
UT was kind of like that benchmark that
UT는 벤치 마크와 비슷했습니다.
everybody used and I mean even even now
모두가 사용하고 지금도 의미
like when I look back on it like I think
내가 생각하는 것처럼 다시 돌아 보면
I had the most fun with UT compared to
나는 UT에 비해 가장 재미있었습니다.
counter-strike or Team Fortress oh yeah
카운터 스트라이크 또는 팀 포트리스
and that was about the time that Jeff
그 시간은 제프가
and I got to know one another
그리고 나는 서로를 알아야한다
yes so and this is part of how we got to
그렇습니다 그리고 이것은 우리가 도착한 방법의 일부입니다
know one another so this is actually
서로를 알기 때문에 이것이 실제로
kind of special to category-five I think
내가 생각하는 카테고리 5에 특별한 종류
Jeff yeah because this game this game
이 게임이 게임이기 때문에 제프 그래
brought us closer together
우리를 더 가깝게했다
what was the other one where we heard
우리가 들었던 다른 것은 무엇 이었습니까
was we played tremulous tremulous
우리는 엄청나게 놀랐 니?
thought formulas is a Linux game where
생각 공식은 리눅스 게임이다
we were like spiders yes aliens and
우리는 거미 예 외계인과 같았고
running around and everything that was
주위를 돌아 다니며
an open source but but tremulous as well
오픈 소스이지만 끔찍한
as Unreal Tournament what was neat about
언리얼 토너먼트로서
this is it was one of the first real
이것은 첫 번째 진짜 중 하나입니다
games that was available on Linux yeah
리눅스에서 사용할 수 있었던 게임
so you can install this directly on
그래서 당신은 이것을 직접 설치할 수 있습니다
Linux now it's a it's called a PC cd-rom
리눅스는 이제 PC CD-ROM이라고 불립니다.
but right on the back you can see tucks
그러나 바로 뒤에 당신은 tucks를 볼 수 있습니다
see that so yes the Installer is for
설치 프로그램이
Windows but it also has an installer for
Windows이지만 설치 프로그램이 있습니다.
Linux so this was I think one of the
리눅스 그래서 이것은 내가 생각
first games so so it made us able to
첫 게임 이니까
play deathmatch multiplayer across we
우리를 가로 질러 데스 매치 멀티 플레이
did land parties yep what was our
파티 파티를 했습니까?
biggest LAN party would you say oh gosh
가장 큰 LAN 파티는 오 세상에
I want to say we had four or five
우리가 4-5 명이라고 말하고 싶어
computers at one point eza yeah do you
한 지점에서 컴퓨터 예 eza 그래
remember the time when we had a LAN
LAN이 있었던 시간을 기억하십시오
party and we had like people sitting I
파티와 우리는 내가 앉아있는 사람들처럼
had like the big 40 inch CRT TV and it
큰 40 인치 CRT TV를 좋아했고
was connected to a computer
컴퓨터에 연결되었습니다
this was like a big land party where we
이것은 우리가 큰 땅 파티처럼
had I don't know maybe 10 or 15 people
내가 아마 10 명 또는 15 명의 사람을 모른다면
over and and we just had an Unreal
우리는 방금 언리얼을 가졌습니다
Tournament land party yes oh that was so
토너먼트 랜드 파티 그래
much fun those were the days love that
그날 사랑했던 많은 재미
yeah I think we need to like have
그래, 우리가 좋아하는 것 같아
another UT land party I think so
또 다른 UT 랜드 파티
20 years in do you think it's still
20 년이 지난 지금도 여전히
worth playing absolutely
절대적으로 재생할 가치
what do you think folks I the Redeemer
당신은 어떻게 구속 자라고 생각합니까?
was my weapon of choice
내가 선택한 무기 였어
well of choice do you remember I I you
선택의 여지가 많습니까 II
know what I think the Redeemer was my
내가 구속 주라고 생각하는 것을 아십시오
go-to as well yeah mainly because I just
그래도 주로 가니까
couldn't catch up with you like for
당신처럼 따라 잡을 수 없었습니다
whatever reason you were really good at
당신이 정말로 잘하는 이유가 무엇이든
fragging me yeah and with the Redeemer
나를 구속하고 구속자와 함께
and I needed to use a Redeemer to at
에 구속 주를 사용해야했습니다
least kind of have some sort of a
최소한 종류의
semblance of fighting back we're so good
반격의 우리는 너무 좋아
so great miss that game Unreal
그 게임 언리얼 너무 그리워
Tournament you can find it on Amazon
토너먼트는 아마존에서 찾을 수 있습니다
still again it's on Steam it is not for
여전히 다시 그것은 증기가 아닙니다.
kids I mean we say that it's it's got a
아이들이 우리는 그것이있어
lot of violence but but it's kind of
폭력은 많지만 일종의
comic mischievous violence and a lot of
만화 장난 폭력과 많은
fun and in fact my kids are old enough
재미 있고 사실 내 아이들은 충분히 나이가 들었습니다
that we're starting to play this
우리는 이것을하기 시작합니다
together now yeah which is really really
함께 지금 그래 정말 정말입니다
cool
시원한
20 years in folks Unreal Tournament so
20 년 동안 언리얼 토너먼트
you know big kudos to the developers of
당신은 개발자에게 큰 명성을 알고
that game are you ready for this Jeff I
그 게임은이 Jeff I 준비가 되었습니까?
want to go through the system
시스템을 통해 가고 싶어
requirements folks at home are you ready
집에 필요한 사람들이 준비 되었습니까?
for this
이를 위해
seriously acquirements yeah okay so I
진지하게 인수 예 그래, 난
want to install this on my I $9.99
내 $ 9.99에 이것을 설치하고 싶습니다
hundred K at five gigahertz with 64 gigs
64 기가있는 5 기가 헤르츠에서 100 K
of RAM but let's make sure we meet the
RAM의 그러나 우리가
minimum system requirements according to
에 따라 최소 시스템 요구 사항
the jewel-case here we go system
여기 보석 케이스
requirements CPU pentium 200 megahertz
CPU 펜티엄 200 메가 헤르츠
or better recommended Pentium to 233 Wow
또는 233 Wow에 추천하는 Pentium
memory 32 megabytes of ram recommended
메모리 32MB의 램 권장
64 megabytes we're not talking gigabytes
우리가 말하지 않는 64 메가 바이트 기가 바이트
here okay we're talking megabytes 64
여기서 우리는 메가 바이트를 이야기하고 있습니다 64
oh my goodness remember when we thought
오 내 선한 생각
that was big yes okay available
그것은 컸습니다 예 가능합니다
harddrive space required to install
설치에 필요한 하드 드라이브 공간
Unreal Tournament back in today yes yeah
오늘의 언리얼 토너먼트 예 예
take a guess for me
나를 추측 해봐
I'm gonna guess 62
나는 62를 추측 할 것이다
megabytes you're you're about half
메가 바이트 당신은 약 절반입니다
halfway there
반쯤
see I was gonna say 120 yeah that's the
내가 120이라고 말할거야 참조 그래
minimum the minimum requirement is a
최소 최소 요구 사항은
hundred and twenty megabytes Wow
백 이십 메가 바이트
megabytes recommended because it's got
그것이 있기 때문에 메가 바이트 권장
remember there are two disks here one of
여기에 두 개의 디스크가 있다는 것을 기억하십시오
them is the game disk one of them is the
그들 중 하나는 게임 디스크입니다
extras if you want the extras you're
엑스트라를 원한다면 엑스트라
gonna need about six hundred and five
약 육백 오가 필요합니다
megabytes they're that specific it
메가 바이트 그들은 특정 특정
actually says 605 megabytes is
실제로 605MB는
recommended okay it's cd-rom Windows 9x
CD-ROM Windows 9x입니다.
compatible I want to read this verbatim
호환 나는이 그대로를 읽고 싶습니다
it says Windows 9x compatible so that
그것은 Windows 9x와 호환되도록
means this was compatible with windows
이것은 Windows와 호환되었음을 의미합니다.
95 and windows 98 yet you can still run
95와 Windows 98은 아직 실행할 수 있습니다
it on Windows 10 and Linux now here in
이제 Windows 10 및 Linux에서
2019 and this of course came out in you
2019 년과 물론 나왔습니다
guessed at 1999 the video PCI local bus
1999 년 비디오 PCI 로컬 버스로 추측
video card 3d accelerator recommended do
비디오 카드 3D 가속기 권장
you think that my Nvidia r-tx 6000 is
내 Nvidia r-tx 6000은
going to be sufficient to play Unreal
언리얼을하기에 충분할 것입니다
Tournament
토너먼트
it only has lag just a little bit I
그것은 단지 약간의 지연이 있습니다.
don't know Jeff it has maybe a little
제프 몰라 조금 있을지도 몰라
bit it only has 24 gigs of DDR 6 ram
비트 6 기가 DDR 6 램만 있음
onboard operating system windows 95
온보드 운영 체제 창 95
windows 98 windows 2000 because we all
우리 모두 때문에 windows 98 windows 2000
played Unreal Tournament on our Windows
Windows에서 언리얼 토너먼트를 플레이했습니다
servers didn't we
서버는 우리를하지 않았다
Windows NT boy a downloadable Linux
다운로드 가능한 Linux 인 Windows NT boy
version is available at Unreal
언리얼에서 사용할 수있는 버전
Tournament com it actually says that
토너먼트 COM은 실제로 말한다
right on the jewel-case here network and
여기 보석 케이스 네트워크에서
internet play via tcp/ip like there
tcp / ip를 통한 인터넷 플레이
because there odin you can't do this
odin 당신이 할 수 없기 때문에
with fidonet folks
fidonet 사람들과 함께
no you need a tcp/ip network that is
아니요, TCP / IP 네트워크가 필요합니다.
just what can I say
내가 뭘 말할 수 있니
unreal that's that's your Unreal
언리얼 그게 당신의 언리얼입니다
Tournament folks happy 20th birthday to
토너먼트에서 행복한 20 번째 생일
the greatest game probably I'd say of
아마 내가 말한 가장 큰 게임
all time that's the ultimate match game
항상 최고의 경기 게임입니다
I should try playing it just once Oh
한 번만 해봐
Sasha I think you should join us for a
사샤 나는 당신이 우리와 함께해야한다고 생각
LAN party because that was before before
그 전에는 LAN 파티
we got to know one another
우리는 서로를 알게되었다
wouldn't it be just a joy folks to have
그것은 단지 기쁨 사람들이 아닌가
Sasha and Jef together and maybe get the
사샤와 제프가 함께 모여
community together to do an unreal
비현실적으로하기 위해 함께 커뮤니티
tournament absolutely annihilated right
토너먼트 절대적으로 소멸
off the hog I think so now because it
내가 생각하기 때문에 돼지에서 떨어져
was so long ago yeah would there be
너무 오래 전에 예 있었을 것입니다
capabilities today of online like server
오늘날의 서버와 같은 온라인 기능
play yes sir it's so it's not direct to
직접 연주하지 않도록 예스 플레이
connect to a specific server it's just
특정 서버에 연결하면
open you could join you you create a
당신이 당신을 만들 수있는 열
server in your game yep and it gives
당신의 게임에 서버 예 그리고 그것은 제공
everyone else access to that server if
다른 모든 사람이 해당 서버에 액세스하는 경우
it's a public server if it's a private
개인 인 경우 공용 서버
server its land only or if somebody has
토지를 서버로
your IP and you've got the ports open on
IP와 포트가 열려 있습니다.
your network then they'll be able to
당신의 네트워크는 그들이 할 수있을 것입니다
play as well who wants to turn it into a
그것으로 바꾸고 싶은 사람뿐만 아니라 재생
VR game well I do have modern version
VR 게임 잘 현대 버전이 있습니다
Sascha
사샤
I mean Unreal Tournament is certainly
언리얼 토너먼트는 확실히
not dead right but this is the original
바로 죽지 않았지만 이것은 원래
the the real deal right here it's too
여기서 진짜 거래는 너무
bad that we couldn't have a bunch of
우리는 무리를 가질 수 없다는 나쁜
copies available for our patrons that
우리 고객들에게 제공되는 사본
way we can that would be great well I
우리가 그렇게 잘할 수있는 방법은
will say if we had let's just say
우리가 방금 말했으면 말할 것입니다
community if you were fans of Unreal
언리얼 팬이라면 커뮤니티
Tournament if you don't already have it
토너먼트가 없으면 토너먼트
grab a copy and steam again it's only 11
사본을 잡고 다시 steam니다. 11
bucks I got this for 6 bucks on Amazon
벅스 아마존에서 6 벅으로 이것을 얻었습니다.
used so you can still get it get it and
당신은 여전히 ​​그것을 얻을 수 있도록 사용
get it installed and up and working and
설치 및 작동 및 작동
then communicate back to us here
다음 우리에게 다시 연락
category 5 TV and let's do it let's
카테고리 5 TV와 해보자
let's do a LAN party guys ok totally be
LAN 파티를 해보자
up for that yeah all right I'm in there
그래 맞아 내가 거기있어
let's do it we played the first like MMO
우리가 MMO와 같은 첫 번째 연주를 해보자
Entropia universe Wow well that was a
엔트로피 아 우주 와우
that was quite a bit later Jeff it was
그것은 꽤 나중에 Jeff이었다
yeah but I mean I do remember playing
그래,하지만 난 내가 기억하는 걸 기억해
that one that was like right at the
바로 그 같은
beginning of mmo's yeah oh yeah it's
mmo의 시작 yeah oh yeah it 's
still exists as well it's still it's
여전히 존재하지만 여전히 존재합니다
still out there I still have my ped so
아직도 거기에 나는 여전히 내 친구를 가지고
do i yeah
내가 그래
don't know if it really helps me out
그것이 정말로 나를 돕는 지 모르겠다
these days I've never cashed out but hey
요즘 나는 돈을 낸 적이 없지만 헤이
I've got some good ingame that's around
주변에 좋은 게임이 있어요
stuff but hey that's so cool 20 years I
물건 그러나 이봐 20 년 정말 멋지다
can't believe it makes me feel a little
내가 조금 느끼게 믿을 수 없어
bit old but at the same time wow that's
조금 낡았지만 동시에 와우
a nostalgia right there well we've got
우리가 가지고있는 향수
to take a really quick break when we
우리가 정말 빠른 휴식을 취할 수
come back we're gonna be looking at a
우리가 돌아올거야 돌아와
new product from Amazon it's called the
아마존의 새로운 제품은
Amazon echo flex you can want to see
보고 싶은 아마존 에코 플렉스
this stick around
이 스틱 주위에
[Music]
[음악]
welcome back this is category five
다시 환영합니다. 이것은 카테고리 5입니다.
technology TV now have you got one of
테크놀로지 TV는 이제
these guys yet I have one yeah yeah I'm
이 녀석들 아직 나는 그래 그래 그래
gonna tell you as we start off this
우리가 이것을 시작할 때 당신에게 말할거야
demonstration if your keywords are
키워드가 데모 인 경우
anything other than Alexa make sure you
Alexa 이외의 것은 당신을 확인
turn off your device or mute the
기기를 끄거나
microphone for the moment because we're
우리가 있기 때문에 순간 마이크
gonna be talking about this and
이것에 대해 이야기하고
demonstrating one of their new devices
새로운 장치 중 하나를 시연
so this is the Amazon echo dot the the
그래서 이것은 아마존 에코 도트입니다
the one that doesn't have the built-in
내장되어 있지 않은 것
clock is the one that I have and this
시계는 내가 가진 것이고
thing sounds great it works great and
일이 잘 들린다
it's fantastic but you've got a wire
환상적이지만 전선이 있습니다.
that comes out of the back for power and
그것은 힘을 위해 뒤에서 나오고
it's gonna take up like death space or a
죽음의 공간이나
counter space or something like that
카운터 공간 또는 그와 비슷한 것
Jeff where is yours residing right now
제프는 지금 어디 계시 니?
ours is in the kitchen sitting on the
우리는 부엌에 앉아
windowsill actually okay to plug right
창턱은 실제로 바로 연결하는 것이 좋습니다
beside the windowsills so that's ideal
창턱 옆에 있으므로 이상적입니다.
we have maybe you know half a foot of
우리는 아마 당신의 반 발을 알고있다
cord yep and so it runs behind the
코드 네 그리고 그것은 뒤에 실행
silverware and then it sits right on the
은 제품은
windowsill and it's perfect it's on
창턱과 그것이 완벽 해
anyway and it's it's got nice acoustics
어쨌든 그것은 좋은 음향 효과가있어
bouncing off the window we use it for
우리가 사용하는 창을 튀는
music in the kitchen all nice that does
부엌에서 좋은 음악
sound really really good but what if
정말 좋은 소리지만 어떻게하면
your plug isn't right next to where the
플러그가 바로 옆에 있지 않습니다
echo is going to be sitting or what if
에코가 앉아 있거나
you just want to be able to plug it
당신은 그것을 연결하고 싶어
directly into the plug wouldn't that be
플러그에 직접 연결되어 있지 않습니다
nice wouldn't that be nice so enter the
멋지지 않을 것이므로 입력하십시오
Amazon echo flex no this is the
아마존 에코 플렉스 아니
brand-new one from Amazon and it is
아마존에서 아주 새로운 것
literally a socket adapter thingy it's a
말 그대로 소켓 어댑터
it's an Amazon echo that you plug in
그것은 당신이 연결하는 아마존 에코입니다
it's got the buttons on the face just
그것은 얼굴에 버튼이 있습니다.
like you just like you expect to be able
당신이 원하는 것처럼 당신처럼
to mute the microphone or activate
마이크를 음소거하거나 활성화
without using the voice command in order
음성 명령을 순서대로 사용하지 않고
to command it and what if they did
명령하고 그들이 한 경우
something a little bit more I mean the
조금 더 의미하는 것은
connectivity on this the physical
이 물리적 연결
connectivity I should say I mean the
연결성 나는
wireless and the smart home connectivity
무선 및 스마트 홈 연결
is excellent but the physical
우수하지만 물리적 인
connectivity is a little bit
연결성은 약간
lacking well this one the Amazon echo
아마존 에코가 부족합니다.
flex oh it's got a USB port it has a USB
flex oh USB 포트가 있고 USB가 있습니다
port and then what if all hypothetical
포트 그리고 모든 가상의 경우
right now it's not hypothetical at all
지금은 전혀 가설이 아닙니다
what if they brought out accessories
그들이 액세서리를 꺼내면 어떨까요?
such as a motion sensor that could just
모션 센서와 같은
plug in like that or say a LED
그런 식으로 연결하거나 LED라고 말하십시오.
nightlight oh nice plug-in like that and
야간 조명 이런 멋진 플러그인과
these are smart home connected so you're
이들은 스마트 홈 연결되어 있으므로
able to control them let's actually I
그들을 제어 할 수 실제로 보자
want to plug this in and see what
이것을 연결하고 무엇을보고 싶어
happens so I've just got this now
이런 일이 생겼으니
obviously this is just like you see it
분명히 이것은 당신이 보는 것처럼
here on your screen you're gonna plug
여기 화면에 플러그를 꽂습니다
this directly into the wall presumably
이것은 아마도 벽에 직접
I'll just say the nice thing about this
나는 이것에 대해 좋은 것을 말할 것입니다.
is the the convenience the portability
휴대가 편리함
and the ability to plug it in anywhere
어디서나 연결할 수있는 기능
you're not gonna get the same sound
넌 같은 소리를 내지 않을거야
quality I mean we come to expect really
품질 우리가 정말 기대한다는 의미
good sound quality out of these guys
이 사람들의 좋은 음질
this one is really about the convenience
이건 정말 편의에 관한 것입니다
and extending the smart home so we've
스마트 홈을 확장하여
already got our smart home kind of built
이미 우리의 스마트 홈 종류를 구축했습니다
up we've got some smart devices we're
우리는 우리가 가진 스마트 장치를 가지고 있습니다
able to control some lamps and things
일부 램프 및 사물을 제어 할 수 있음
like that so this now puts more
이렇게 더 많이 넣습니다
microphones some motion sensors and
마이크 일부 모션 센서 및
things like that around the house on the
집 주변에서 그런 것들
cheap so I'm gonna plug this in just
싸구려 난 그냥 이것을 연결합니다
like I would into the wall and let's see
내가 벽에 들어가서 보자
how difficult this is to to actually
이게 실제로 어려워요
activate so on my smart phone here I'm
여기 내 스마트 폰에서 활성화하십시오.
gonna add a device and I'm gonna go
장치를 추가하고 갈거야
Amazon echo and let's scroll the list
아마존 에코와 목록을 스크롤하자
look at all the devices that they've got
그들이 가진 모든 장치를 봐
already it's a growing line and there's
벌써 성장하고 있으며
the echo flex is it plugged in and
에코 플렉스가 연결되어 있고
orange yup select your Amazon echo
오렌지 p 아마존 에코를 선택
there's only one it's already picked it
이미 고른 것이 하나뿐입니다
up select your Wi-Fi network
Wi-Fi 네트워크를 선택하십시오
all right it's the first one perfect
좋아, 첫 번째 완벽 해
could it be that easy I haven't even had
내가 한 적이없는 것이 쉬울 수 있을까
to configure anything so but this will
아무것도 구성하지 않아도됩니다.
be connected to your specific device oh
특정 장치에 연결되어 있습니다
yeah just showed right up in my app okay
네 그냥 내 앱에 바로 나타났습니다
sweet so now okay scroll through it's
달콤 해 이제 스크롤 해
connected to my Wi-Fi I didn't have to
내 Wi-Fi에 연결되어 있지 않아도
configure that well I've got all these
잘 구성하면이 모든 것을 얻었습니다.
all the options that you would expect
당신이 기대하는 모든 옵션
from any Amazon echo device now I just
이제 모든 Amazon 에코 장치에서
saw it setup pair gadget sure is that
페어 가제트 설정을 확인하십시오.
the devices that go at the bottom well
바닥에 잘 들어가는 장치
let's let's try Jeff I'm gonna plug this
제프를 해보자
guy in Oh first of all here changing the
오에있는 사람이 먼저 여기를 변경
wake word to cancel and then I want to
취소 단어를 깨우고 싶습니다
plug this in no those are those are
이것들을 연결하지 마십시오.
devices like if you have subwoofers or
서브 우퍼가 있거나
other peripherals this guy as soon as I
다른 주변기기들이 사람은
plug it in it's gonna flash oh there we
플러그를 꽂아 플래시시켜
go
가기
it looks like it's connecting nice okay
잘 연결되고있는 것 같습니다
so now Jeff I'm gonna add a routine okay
이제 제프 난 일상을 추가 할거야
and I'm gonna create new and I'm gonna
그리고 나는 새로운 것을 만들거야
add an action and this really reminds me
액션을 추가하면 실제로 저를 생각 나게합니다.
of like if this then that right so I'm
이게 바로 그런 것 같아서
gonna jump into my smart home because
내 똑똑한 집으로 뛰어들거야
that's where this device is going to
그것이이 장치가가는 곳입니다
show up and you see there's my motion
나타나고 내 움직임이있는 걸 봤어
sensor and if we detect motion I want to
센서와 움직임을 감지하면
do what let's add an action so when the
때 행동을 추가하자 무엇을 할
sensor detects motion I guess it says
센서가 움직임을 감지합니다.
and I cancel
그리고 나는 취소한다
I can select something okay cancel let's
괜찮은 걸 선택할 수 있습니다
go into my smart home and and look at my
내 똑똑한 집으로 가서
devices there's my Christmas tree at the
장치에는 내 크리스마스 트리가 있습니다
top for example okay so let's just say
예를 들어 좋아, 그냥 말해 보자
turn it on so as soon as it
최대한 빨리 켜십시오
Tech's motion it's going to turn on my
테크의 움직임
Christmas tree is this the Christmas
크리스마스 트리는 이것이 크리스마스
tree you have at home yeah yes exactly
당신이 집에있는 나무 그래 그래 정확히
so as you're moving that around your
당신이 당신의 주위를 이동으로
Christmas tree is going nuts right now
크리스마스 트리는 지금 미쳐 가고있다
yeah I guess so
맞아, 그런가 봐
no if it's already on its a it's it's
아니 이미 그것에 있다면 그것은
gonna be on but now I can put this in
에 있지만 지금은 이것을 넣을 수 있습니다
the hallway leading up to the room where
복도로 이어지는 복도
the Christmas tree is and as soon as
크리스마스 트리는 곧
somebody walks by if the Christmas tree
누군가가 크리스마스 트리를 지나면
is off it will now turn on because it's
꺼져 있기 때문에 이제 켜져 있습니다.
plugged into my smart power bar so now
이제 스마트 파워 바에 꽂았습니다
okay so I'm gonna I'm gonna disconnect
알았어 그래서 내가 끊을거야
this guy and plug in this and let's just
이 녀석과 이것을 연결하고 그냥하자
see what happens the first time that we
우리가 처음에 무슨 일이 일어나는지보십시오
plug this in that's the nightlight yeah
이것을 야간 조명에 연결하십시오.
I found first light and you can control
첫 번째 조명을 발견하면 제어 할 수 있습니다
it by saying turn off first light I love
내가 사랑하는 첫 번째 빛을 끄라고 말함으로써
what I love about this is how intuitive
내가 좋아하는 것은 얼마나 직관적입니까
it is right anyone can figure this out
누구나 알아낼 수 있습니다.
there's no instruction manual that I
내가 사용 설명서가 없습니다
have to read I'm just so it just told me
읽어야 해 그냥 말해
so I'm gonna try this turn on first
먼저이 차례를 시도하겠습니다
light okay
가벼워 요
set first light to purple okay a set
첫 번째 표시등을 자주색으로 설정
first light to red now on camera you're
카메라의 첫 번째 표시등이 빨간색으로 바 now
not really seeing how red that really is
그게 정말 빨간색인지 보지 못하고
no but we're in the studio
아니하지만 우리는 스튜디오에있어
are you yeah yeah okay in the it's it's
당신은 그래 그래 그래 괜찮아
interesting how LED reacts to our 60
LED가 60에 어떻게 반응하는지
Hertz cameras right change first light
Hertz 카메라, 첫 번째 조명 변경
to orange yep and there is a shift in
오렌지색으로 바뀌면
the color yeah okay change first light
색상 예 좋아 첫 번째 빛을 변경
to purple okay there you go okay you can
보라색으로 가도 괜찮습니다.
see it on my hand nice and clear no
내 손에 잘 보이네
apparently that's the secret
분명히 그 비밀이야
now Marshman is saying in the chat room
이제 Marshman이 대화방에서 말합니다
yeah
네
give her a instruction to change the
그녀에게
color to whatever but don't say okay is
괜찮지 만 말하지 않는 것은 무엇이든
that an instruction you can give with
당신이 줄 수있는 지시
this device because every time it's like
이 장치는 항상
okay okay okay is there a problem with
알았어 알았어 알았어
that no but like I'm thinking for
아니,하지만 내가 생각하고있는 것처럼
instance you know if you've got a kid
예를 들어 아이가 있다면
who say has a nightlight in their room
누가 방에 야간 조명이 있다고
yeah they might just say turn the light
예, 그들은 단지 빛을 켜라고 말할 수도 있습니다.
on
에
yeah and you don't want to have this
그래 그리고 너는 이것을 원하지 않아
voice coming back to you in the middle
중간에 당신에게 다시 오는 목소리
and I go on okay sure I'll make that
내가 계속 할게요
happen is this bright enough for you
이런 일이 당신을 위해 충분히 밝습니까
like a whisper or something you probably
속삭임 또는 아마도 당신이 뭔가
can just because Jeff wants to know
Jeff가 알고 싶어서
volume zero
볼륨 제로
turn off the first light volume eight
첫 번째 빛 볼륨을 끄십시오.
turn on first light
첫 번째 조명을 켜십시오
okay all right volume zero
알았어.
turn off first light
첫 번째 조명을 끄십시오
turn on first light
첫 번째 조명을 켜십시오
okay oh she said it all right
오, 그녀는 괜찮아 말했다
does it matter no no but I just it was
아무 상관 없어요하지만 난 그냥
an interesting comment in the in the
의 흥미로운 의견
chatroom and I was like you know what
대화방과 나는 당신이 무엇을 알고있는 것처럼
okay that's a good question especially
좋아요, 특히 좋은 질문입니다
if you've got say kids sleeping at night
밤에 아이들이 자고 있다고하면
because it is a nightlight you could set
그것은 당신이 설정할 수있는 야간 조명이기 때문에
it to be almost like a little bit of a
그것은 거의 조금처럼
gentle wake up to trip they set it to
그들은 여행을 설정
automatically come on at certain times
특정 시간에 자동으로 켜집니다
that it turn off my first light
내 첫 번째 조명을 끄는
can you set first light to come on at
에 첫 번째 조명을 켤 수 있습니까
7:00 a.m. oh she thinks is the first
오전 7시 오, 그녀는 처음이라고 생각
motion Center says so there are you know
모션 센터에 따르면
there's probably gonna be help for that
아마 도움이 될 것입니다
kind of stuff right yeah whether like
그래 좋아하는 물건의 종류
you can set up routines though so in my
그래도 루틴을 설정할 수 있습니다.
app I can set up the routine to do
내가 할 루틴을 설정할 수있는 응용 프로그램
certain things as I mentioned it it
내가 언급 한대로
really has a reminiscent look to if this
이 경우 정말 연상적인 모습을
then that so if a certain time is
특정 시간이되면
approached automatically do whatever
접근은 자동적으로 무엇이든한다
right I would within the next bike I
바로 다음 자전거 내에서
have to wake up in the next hour yeah
다음 시간에 일어나야합니다
change color to a different color so
색을 다른 색으로 바꾸면
that when I kind of opened my eyes it's
내가 눈을 뜨면 그것은
not it's a nightlight if this this one
이건 이건 야간이야
is a nightlight
야경이야
right so this is the one that's gonna go
바로 이것이 갈 것입니다
in the hall for what you want to do I
네가하고 싶은 일을 홀에서
would get a smart power bar for example
예를 들어 스마트 파워 바를 얻을 것
and have it plugged into a lamp and have
램프에 연결하고
it I have it turn on or get one that can
그것은 내가 켜거나 할 수있는 하나를 얻을
fade up for example or you can actually
예를 들어 페이드 업하거나 실제로
get smart lamps that will bring the the
스마트 램프를 가져옵니다
light up like sunlight like a like a so
이렇게 햇빛처럼 불이 켜집니다
you get these various devices so this
다양한 장치를 얻을 수 있습니다.
particular one again it's it's really
다시 한 번 그것은 정말이야
really cheap and it's something that you
정말 싸고 당신이 뭔가
can just plug in anywhere in the house
집안 어디에서나 연결 가능
and it extends that that smart home so
스마트 홈을 확장시켜
that no matter where you are it will
당신이 어디에 있든
play music it it can be a controller for
음악 재생 그것은 그것을 위해 컨트롤러가 될 수 있습니다
your voice-activated things throughout
당신의 음성 활성화 물건
the house and and it's all done it's the
집과 모든 일이 끝났습니다.
exact same so the questions are like you
똑같이 질문이 당신처럼
can it do this kind of do that it's
이런 종류의 일을 할 수 있습니까?
exactly the same as this guy as far as
이 남자와 정확히 같은
the commands go right so it could
명령이 제대로 진행되도록
broadcasts to the whole family to all
온 가족에게 모든 방송
devices like if dinner right like you
너처럼 저녁을 먹는다면
could just talk to it it can and I don't
그냥 말해도 돼요
want to demonstrate that I do
내가하는 것을 보여주고 싶다
have some echo devices at home but you
집에 반향 장치가 있지만
can well how could I do that drop in
내가 어떻게 그 드롭을 할 수 있을까
right no so I haven't Alexa device in my
아니, 그래서 내 Alexa 장치를하지 않은
kitchen that's why it asked and I'm
그게 왜 냐고 내가 요구하는 주방
holding it like a walkie-talkie you
워키 토키처럼 잡고
don't have to hold it like that you're
당신이 그런 식으로 붙잡을 필요가 없습니다
gonna have it plugged in somewhere else
다른 곳에 연결해
in the house and is a sensitive enough I
집안에 있고 나는 충분히 민감하다
mean drop in
평균 하락
right now because you're already in a
이미 당신이 있기 때문에
conversation Oh cancel hang up I didn't
대화 오 취소 끊지 않았다
realize I was in a conversation Oh so
내가 대화중임을 알았어
home is listening so that is the new
듣고있는 새 집
echo flex I mean this is a really really
에코 플렉스 이것은 정말 정말 의미
I mean I hate to use the term but it's a
나는이 용어를 사용하는 것을 싫어하지만
smart device if it wasn't for such a
그렇지 않은 경우 스마트 장치
dumb user but you just literally just
바보 같은 사용자지만 당신은 말 그대로
plug that in anywhere in your house or
집안 어느 곳에 나 연결하거나
your office and we can have these
당신의 사무실과 우리는 이것을 가질 수 있습니다
anywhere so as long as they have Wi-Fi
Wi-Fi가있는 한 어디서나
connectivity you can have devices at
연결 가능한 기기
home you can have devices at work if you
집에 있으면 직장에서 기기를 사용할 수 있습니다
like presumably like in my situation I'm
아마 내 상황 에서처럼
in a small office so I could have that
작은 사무실에서
at work I could have one here at the
직장에서 나는 여기에 하나를 가질 수
studio and I can use it to communicate
스튜디오와 의사 소통에 사용할 수 있습니다
with home I can use it to listen to
집에서 나는 그것을 듣고 사용할 수 있습니다
music in various places I can use the
다양한 장소에서 음악을 사용할 수 있습니다.
one at the studio to set up alerts that
스튜디오에서 하나는 경고를 설정
will notify me at home for example so
예를 들어 집에서 알려줍니다
it's just an extension of your smart
그것은 단지 당신의 똑똑한 확장입니다
home and that's the echo flex from
집에서 나오는 에코 플렉스입니다.
Amazon you can get one at cap five dot
아마존 당신은 모자 다섯 점 하나를 얻을 수 있습니다
TV slash echo now given that it is
이제 TV 슬래시 에코
something that you would be buying from
당신이 구입할 것
Amazon yeah
아마존 예
for today's episode and I mean it is
오늘의 에피소드와 나는
what are we we are on November 27th
우리는 11 월 27 일에 무엇입니까
we're about something if you're watching
우리는 당신이보고 있다면 뭔가에 관한 것입니다
live yeah if you're watching live but if
라이브 예, 라이브를보고 있다면
you're watching this recorded this is
당신은 이것을 기록하고 있습니다.
done at November 27th and so Black
11 월 27 일에 이렇게 블랙
Friday starts as of midnight right just
금요일 자정부터 바로 시작
a few short hours for Amazon their Black
아마존 블랙에 대한 짧은 시간
Friday deals starts so I mean if you're
금요일 거래가 시작 되니
gonna if you're sitting there going yeah
네가 거기 앉아 있으면 갈거야
you know what I think I'm gonna pick up
내가 뭘 생각하는지 알아
a couple of these for those don't forget
그 중 몇 가지를 잊지 마세요
our partner links because that's a way
그 방법이기 때문에 우리의 파트너 링크
to kick back to us with a little bit of
약간의 우리와 함께 우리를 반동
cash in the jars and help pay for all
항아리에 현금을 모두 지불
the stuff that we do here and so if
우리가 여기서하는 것들과
you're gonna be buying your various
당신은 당신의 다양한 구매 할거야
devices or anything else from Amazon
장치 또는 아마존의 다른 것
maybe you're getting some early
어쩌면 당신은 일찍 얻을거야
Christmas shopping it don't forget to
잊지 못할 크리스마스 쇼핑
chat idea partner likes yeah not really
아이디어 파트너가 좋아하는 채팅 예
if like when yeah take advantage of the
예 때 활용하는 경우
sales it's category 5 TV slash partners
판매 카테고리 5 TV 슬래시 파트너
we'll get you there Sasha it's time to
우리는 당신을 거기에 데려 갈 시간입니다 사샤
head over to the newsroom are you all
뉴스 룸으로 가십시오
set sure em here's what's coming up in
여기에 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 확인하십시오.
the category 5 TV news
카테고리 5 TV 뉴스
the Department of National Defense is
국방부는
joining the fight against 5g citing
5g 인용과의 싸움에 합류
risks to GPS and military operations
GPS 및 군사 작전에 대한 위험
google is serious about ensuring the
구글은
pixel line of Android phones is secure
안드로이드 폰의 픽셀 라인은 안전합니다
they've announced that they'll pay
그들은 그들이 지불 할 것이라고 발표했습니다
security researchers up to 1.5 million
최대 150 만 명의 보안 연구원
dollars to find hacks and exploits the
해킹과 익스플로잇을 찾기위한 달러
official site for the Monaro digital
Monaro 디지털 공식 사이트
coin was hacked to deliver currency
동전은 통화를 제공하기 위해 해킹
stealing malware to users who were
사용자에게 악성 코드를 훔치는 행위
downloading wallet software and wouldn't
지갑 소프트웨어 다운로드
it be nice if there is a Facebook rival
페이스 북 라이벌이 있으면 좋겠다
well there is and it's founded by the
잘 있고 그것은에 의해 설립
guy who built Wikipedia
Wikipedia를 만든 사람
stick around the full details are coming
모든 세부 사항이 다가오고 있습니다.
up later in the show this is the
나중에 쇼에서 이것은
category 5 dot TV newsroom covering the
카테고리 5 닷 TV 뉴스 룸
week stop texting with a slight linux
약간의 리눅스로 문자 메시지 중지
bias I'm Sacha Rickman joined this week
Sacha Rickman입니다 편견 이번 주에 가입
by Jeff Westen here's some quick
Jeff Westen이 여기 몇 가지 빠릅니다.
honorable mentions this week Tesla CEO
이번 주 테슬라 CEO
Elon Musk
엘론 머스크
suggested late Tuesday that his company
화요일 늦은 그의 회사 제안
had now received 250,000 pre-orders for
에 대한 250,000 선주문을 받았습니다
the cyber truck it's Blade Runner
사이버 트럭 블레이드 러너
inspired electric pickup Tesla's unveil
영감을 얻은 전기 픽업 테슬라의 공개
event for its first pickup truck was
첫 픽업 트럭 행사는
marred by the vehicles window breaking
차량 창문이 망가졌다
when an executive threw a meatball at
임원이 미트볼을 던졌을 때
them in an effort to demo some Ron
Ron을 시연하기 위해
Burgundy all right well anyway so ladies
어쨌든 잘 부르고뉴
and gentlemen there was a apparently a
신사 여러분, 분명히
meatball that went through the window
창문을 통과 한 미트볼
you know just keep going after the
당신은 그냥 계속 계속 알고
meatball Jeff it turns out the safe test
미트볼 제프, 안전한 테스트 결과
was performed before in fact that went
실제로 갔다 전에 수행
perfectly the cars trapezoid shape was
완벽하게 자동차 사다리꼴 모양이었다
also mocked in various memes even the
또한 다양한 밈에 조롱
official social media pages for Lego had
레고의 공식 소셜 미디어 페이지는
their go at the cyber truck but included
사이버 트럭에 갔지만 포함
innovative
혁신적인
roof racks mr. musk has said on Twitter
루프랙 씨 사향은 트위터에 말했다
that the recent cyber truck is so
최근 사이버 트럭은
cleaner is that it can't stamp ultra
클리너는 울트라 스탬프를 할 수 없다는 것입니다
hard 30 times steel because it breaks
30 배의 강철이 부러지기 때문에
the stamping press despite the initial
초기에도 불구하고 스탬핑 프레스
social media storm on people mocking the
사람들을 조롱하는 사람들의 소셜 미디어 폭풍
trucks design others had praised the
다른 사람들을 칭찬했던 트럭 디자인
cyber track for bringing something new
새로운 것을 가져다주는 사이버 트랙
to the table wise cam owners will soon
테이블 현명한 캠 소유자에게 곧
find an update removes the AI driven
AI로 구동되는 업데이트를 찾으십시오.
person detection from their device due
기기로 인한 사람 감지
to the unexpected termination of the
의 예기치 않은 종료
agreement Waze had with their AI
Waze와 AI의 계약
provider in waze's commitment wise wise
현명한 현명한 약속의 공급자
oh my gosh
이런
meatball ways for free they're stating
그들이 말하는 미트볼 방법 무료
that their own AI division to bring back
AI 부서에서
person direction and other AI
사람 방향 및 기타 AI
improvements to the motion detection
동작 감지 개선
wise is being praised by its users on
현명한 사용자에 의해 칭찬되고있다
social media for their transparency
투명성을위한 소셜 미디어
though what is not the what is no doubt
의심의 여지가없는 것은 아니지만
a difficult situation for their staff
직원들에게 어려운 상황
the new firmware which removes the AI
AI를 제거하는 새로운 펌웨어
features is planned for mid-january 2020
기능은 2020 년 1 월 중순에 예정되어 있습니다.
there's no ETA yet as to when their new
그들의 새로운 때 아직 아직 도착 시간이 없습니다
in-house solution will be ready let's
사내 솔루션 준비 완료
get into the top stories we're following
우리가 팔로우하는 주요 스토리에 들어가십시오
this week the Department of Defense is
이번 주 국방부는
joining the fight against 5g citing
5g 인용과의 싸움에 합류
risks to GPS and military operations the
GPS 및 군사 작전에 대한 위험
issue is with a proposal before the
문제는 전에 제안과 함께
Federal Communications Commission to
연방 통신위원회
open the 1 to 2 gigahertz frequency
1 ~ 2 기가 헤르츠 주파수 열기
range the L band for use in 5g cellular
5g 셀룰러에 사용하기위한 L 대역 범위
networks the problem is that some of
네트워크 문제는
those frequencies are already in use by
그 주파수는 이미
the global positioning system and other
글로벌 포지셔닝 시스템 및 기타
military systems in a letter to FCC
FCC에 편지로 군사 시스템
Chairman a edgy PI Secretary of Defense
초초 PI 국방 장관 회장
Mark Esper pressed for the rejection of
마크 에스퍼는 거부 거부
the proposal saying quote there are too
견적을 말하는 제안도 있습니다
many unknowns and the risks are far too
많은 미지수와 위험도 너무 멀다
great to federal operations to allow the
연방 운영에 큰
proposed system to proceed this could
이를 진행할 수있는 제안 된 시스템
have a significant negative impact on
에 중대한 부정적인 영향을 미치다
military operations both in peacetime
평화 시간에 군사 작전
and war end quote while supporters of
지지자들은
the proposal asite the low power of the
제안 사이트의 저전력
transmitters and say this should not
송신기는 말하지 말라고
cause interference studies performed in
간섭 연구를 수행하다
show that GPS signals arriving from
GPS 신호가
space could be overpowered by even low
공간은 심지어 낮게 압도 될 수 있습니다
powered ground-based transmissions
강화 된 지상 전송
thanks to the inverse-square law a
역 제곱 법 덕분에
report from the national space-based
국가 우주 기반 보고서
positioning navigation and timing
위치 탐색 및 타이밍
systems engineering forum noted that the
시스템 엔지니어링 포럼은
tests demonstrated that there are
테스트는
significantly detrimental impacts to all
모두에게 중대한 해로운 영향
GPS applications assessed and quote and
GPS 응용 프로그램 평가 및 인용
if either we're like approaching that
우리가 접근하는 것과 같다면
time when there just aren't enough
충분하지 않은 시간
frequencies left like do you think that
남은 주파수는
we're almost there yeah it sounds like
우린 거의 다 왔어 그래
we're there they're using frequencies
우리는 그들이 주파수를 사용하고 있습니다
that are already in use there are more
이미 사용중인 더 많은
frequencies we can just tap into let's
우리가 탭할 수있는 주파수
jump into the 50 gigahertz band and see
50 기가 헤르츠 대역으로 점프
what it does to our brains like that's
그것이 우리의 뇌에하는 일
the thing alright it's safe we've had
우리가 가지고있는 것이 안전합니다
Wi-Fi interviews covering in the past
과거의 Wi-Fi 인터뷰
how they want to split up the way that
그들이 방법을 나누고 싶어
they're doing Wi-Fi in the home so it
그들은 집에서 Wi-Fi를하고 있습니다.
makes me wonder if there's a way to take
취할 방법이 있는지 궁금해합니다
some of these bands and kind of do the
이 밴드들 중 일부는
same deal you know because it was I
내가했기 때문에 당신도 알고있는 거래
forget what the technology was called
기술이 무엇인지 잊어 버려
but it was an innovative new approach
하지만 혁신적인 새로운 접근 방식이었습니다
that basically was kind of like you know
기본적으로 당신이 아는 것처럼
adding more lanes to a highway when it
고속도로에 차선 추가
comes to Wi-Fi and so I wonder if
Wi-Fi에 와서
something like that could add more bands
그런 밴드는 더 많은 것을 추가 할 수 있습니다
without necessarily boosting to a higher
반드시 더 높은 것으로 부스트하지 않고
power but you still need in order to
힘 그러나 당신은 여전히
have more bands if you will using your
당신이 사용하는 경우 더 많은 밴드가
terms if you need more frequencies right
더 많은 주파수가 필요한 경우 용어
so but if they put things on I think
하지만 그들이 물건을 쓰면
what the issue here is the misconception
여기서 문제는 오해입니다.
that terrestrial low powered broadcast
지상파 저전력 방송
will not interfere with the big powerful
큰 강력한 방해하지 않습니다
satellites that have really powerful
정말 강력한 위성
broadcast well thanks to the
덕분에 잘 방송
inverse-square exactly anybody who has
정확히 제곱을 가진 사람
ever done karaoke knows that if you take
노래방을 해본 적이 있다면
the left and right channel and invert
좌우 채널과 반전
one of them and overlap them you get a
그들 중 하나와 겹치는 당신은 얻을
mono signal and it takes the vocals out
모노 신호와 보컬을 꺼냅니다
well how does that happen
어떻게 그런 일이
it happens because typically vocals are
일반적으로 보컬이 있기 때문에 발생합니다.
in the middle so it by in inverting your
중간에 반전 시켜서
phasing out the middle channel so
중간 채널을 페이징하면
similarly you're gonna get an like that
마찬가지로 당신은 그렇게 얻을거야
kind of
거의
fact we're two overlapping signals
사실 우리는 두 개의 겹치는 신호입니다
you're going to cause interference that
간섭을 일으킬 수 있습니다.
is going to actually phase out certain
실제로 특정 단계를 폐지 할 것입니다
portions of that signal and I think
그 신호의 일부와 나는 생각
that's the concern that has been brought
그것이 제기 된 관심사입니다
forward but of course those who are
앞으로 그러나 물론 사람들
creating the low powered terrestrial
저전력 지상파 생성
signals are saying oh no these are just
신호는 오 아니오 이것들은 단지
low powered signals it's not going to
저전력 신호가 발생하지 않습니다.
cause any problem but meanwhile yeah
문제가 생겼지 만 그동안 그래
there's a very real chance that it could
정말 가능성이 있습니다
so I wonder what the solution would be I
그래서 나는 해결책이 무엇인지 궁금합니다.
would think that the military should
군대가해야한다고 생각
probably have a frequency that couldn't
아마 못했던 주파수가
be like the alb and thing is they've
alb와 같고 물건은
they've been using their own band but
그들은 자신의 밴드를 사용하고 있지만
that but the issue I think is that I
하지만 제가 생각하는 문제는
mean I'm speculating because I'm not on
내가 있지 않기 때문에 내가 추측하고 있음을 의미
the inner circle of the US military
미군의 내원
obviously I can't even get a meatball
분명히 나는 ​​미트볼을 얻을 수 없습니다
right but the thing is the military has
맞지만 문제는 군대가
always been ahead of the curve when it
그것이 항상 곡선보다 앞서
comes to technology yes and it makes me
예 기술에 와서 나를 만듭니다
wonder if we've kind of hit this period
우리가이시기에 맞았는지 궁금해
in in our world where technology is
기술이있는 세상에서
starting to advance faster than what the
무엇보다 빨리 진행하기 시작
military can advance and so the issue
군대는 전진 할 수 있고
they're running into is that society is
그들은 사회가
catching up right and so is it possible
따라 잡기 가능하다
that we're reaching a point I mean not
우리는 내가 의미하지 않는 지점에 도달하고
even just about a signal but that in
심지어 신호에 관한 것입니다.
general the world has started to nip at
일반적으로 세계가 훔치기 시작했습니다
the heels of military advancement
군사 발전의 발 뒤꿈치
because of so many companies and so many
너무 많은 회사와 너무 많은 때문에
smart people out there doing crazy
똑똑한 사람들이 미친 짓을
things under personal Enterprise that
개인 기업에서
the military is going can we keep up
군대는 가고있다 우리는 유지할 수있다
right and what does this mean yeah I
맞아 그리고 이것이 무엇을 의미 하는가
kind of stay ahead of that curve yes
그 곡선보다 앞서있어
then they say okay no more 5g really to
그럼 그들은 더 이상 5g 더 이상 말하지
233 computers because that's I mean
233 대의 컴퓨터이기 때문에
that's the only thing they can do right
그것이 그들이 할 수있는 유일한 일입니다
now it really would mess with their
이제는 정말
safety right their security and well I
안전 바로 그들의 보안과 난
mean look at I'm gonna say was a couple
내 말은 내가 부부라고 말할거야
years ago we had that whole GPS issue
몇 년 전에 우리는 전체 GPS 문제가 있었다
where people were using their Fitbit at
사람들이 Fitbit을 사용하는 곳
secret military base and it was pointing
비밀 군사 기지와 그것을 가리키는
up on a map yeah because they're walking
그들이 걷고 있기 때문에 그래지도에
around like technology has reached a
같은 기술에 도달했습니다
point where we're going
우리가가는 곳을 가리킨다
what kind of other implications are we
우리는 어떤 다른 의미를 지니고 있습니까?
not paying attention to that just seems
그것에주의를 기울이지 않는 것
so benign but really is a big concern
너무 양성이지만 정말 큰 관심사입니다
and this is one where the military may
그리고 이것은 군대가 할 수있는 곳입니다
actually have a very legit concern going
실제로 매우 합법적 인 우려가 있습니다
this could be a national security risk
이것은 국가 안보 위험이 될 수 있습니다
if we have you know special signals that
우리가 특별한 신호를 알고 있다면
get intercepted by Joe Blow with his you
Joe Blow가 당신과 함께 가로 채다
know low frequency stuff at home it's
집에서 저주파 물건을 알고
very true I don't know I don't even I
난 사실조차 몰라요
don't know how to properly answer the
제대로 대답하는 방법을 모른다
concern to be honest I don't either but
정직한 관심사 나도 아니지만
it's an interesting story to follow for
따라야 할 흥미로운 이야기입니다
her mm-hmm Google is serious about
그녀의 mm-hmm Google은
ensuring the pixel line of Android
안드로이드의 픽셀 라인을 보장
phones is secure they've announced that
전화가 안전하다고 발표했습니다
they'll pay security researchers up to
그들은 보안 연구원들에게
1.5 million dollars to find hacks and
해킹을 찾기위한 150 만 달러
exploits the company said Thursday that
목요일 회사는 악용
effective immediately they'll pay 1
그들은 즉시 지불합니다 효과적인 1
million dollars for a quote full chain
견적 전체 체인에 백만 달러
remote code execution exploit with
원격 코드 실행 악용
persistent which compromises the Titan M
Titan M을 손상시키는 지속적
secure element on pixel devices and
픽셀 장치의 보안 요소
quote they'll also pay $500,000 for
그들이 또한 $ 500,000를 지불 할 것을 인용하십시오
exploits that covertly steal data from a
은밀히 데이터를 훔치는 악용
pixel or bypass its lock screen Google
픽셀을 잠 그거나 잠금 화면을 우회
will offer a 50% bonus to any of its
그것의 50 % 보너스를 제공 할 것입니다
rewards if the exploit works on specific
익스플로잇이 특정에서 작동하는 경우 보상
Developer Preview versions of Android
Android의 개발자 미리보기 버전
that means a critical Titan M hack on a
그것은 중요한 타이탄 M에 대한 해킹을 의미
Developer Preview could fetch 1.5
개발자 미리보기에서 1.5를 가져올 수 있음
million dollars and a data exfiltration
백만 달러와 데이터 유출
or lock screen bypass could earn 750
또는 잠금 화면 우회로 750을 얻을 수 있습니다
thousand dollars and so on
천 달러 등
previously rewards for the most severe
이전에 가장 심한 것에 대한 보상
Android exploits topped out at $200,000
안드로이드 익스플로잇 20 만 달러 돌파
the big reward bump coincides with the
큰 보상 범프는
investments Google has poured into
구글 투자에 부어
securing the pixel the Titan M is a
타이탄 M 픽셀을 고정
Google designed chip that's physically
물리적 인 Google 설계 칩
segregated from the main chipset of the
메인 칩셋에서 분리
device Titan M was first introduced in
Titan M 장치는
2018 with the rollout of the pixel 3
픽셀 3의 출시와 함께 2018
it's also in the recently released pixel
최근에 출시 된 픽셀에도 있습니다.
3a and will also be included in the just
3a는 또한 단지에 포함됩니다
released pixel for security researcher
보안 연구원 용 픽셀 출시
Salim Rashid suspects we're in the midst
Salim Rashid는 우리가 중간에 있다고 의심합니다
of an iOS Android security paradigm
iOS 안드로이드 보안 패러다임
shift
시프트
to understand the significance of
의 중요성을 이해하기 위해
Google's announcement third party
Google의 공지 사항 제 3 자
exploit brokers 0 diem will pay hackers
익스플로러 브로커 0 diem은 해커에게 지불합니다
$100,000 to weaponize a lockscreen
잠금 화면을 무기화하기 위해 $ 100,000
bypass on either iOS or Android Google
iOS 또는 Android Google에서 우회
are offering up to seven and a half
최대 7시 반을 제공하고 있습니다
times as much Wow so that's that's
많은 시간 와우 그래서 그것은
really just smart thinking really
정말 똑똑한 생각 정말
because it's worth the money to pay to
돈을 지불 할 가치가 있기 때문에
make sure that there isn't going to be
없을 것임을 확인하십시오
an exploit by somebody malicious you
악의적 인 누군가의 악용
great you just really want to be I guess
당신은 정말 내가되고 싶어 위대한
you want to be enticing enough that
당신은 충분히 유혹하고 싶어
nobody's going to pay more for the
아무도 더 많은 돈을 지불하지 않을 것입니다
exploit right and what you yeah and you
옳고 당신이 원하는 것과 착취하는 것
may as well use it for good right if if
다음과 같은 경우에도 잘 사용할 수 있습니다
someone's gonna hack the operating
누군가가 운영을 해킹 할거야
system of an android device a pixel
안드로이드 장치의 시스템 픽셀
device may as well give them enough
장치는 충분히 제공 할 수 있습니다
incentive that instead of selling that
인센티브를 판매하는 대신
to the bad guys yes sell it directly to
나쁜 사람들에게 네 직접 판매
Google so that they can fix it and
그들이 고칠 수 있도록 구글
you're gonna get seven and a half times
당신은 일곱 번 반 얻을거야
right I would do it for good and also
맞아 내가 잘하고
for $750,000 no I mean this sounds
750,000 달러에 나는 이것이 들린다는 것을 의미한다
self-serving I mean not for myself
자기 봉사 나 자신을 위해 의미하지
because I have no clue how to even go
가는 방법도 전혀 없기 때문에
down that road I am NOT a hacker cracker
그 길 아래로 나는 해커 크래커가 아니다
at all but this seems like as a
전혀하지만 이것은 마치
potential self-serving problem for
잠재적 인 자립 문제
somebody who goes I found the exploit
누군가가 내가 악용을 발견
yeah I found the problem
그래 나는 문제를 발견했다
Google I realize you're offering 1.5
Google은 귀하가 1.5를 제공한다는 것을 알고 있습니다
million but I can sell it on the black
백만이지만 블랙에 팔 수 있습니다
market for 4 million but they can't they
4 백만에 대한 시장이지만 그들은 할 수 없습니다
cannot that's the thing they can sell it
그것이 그들이 팔 수있는 것은 아닙니다
for a hundred thousand so Google sang
십만 명이 구글을 노래
will give you seven and a half times
일곱 번 반 줄 것이다
that exactly Google is totally out
정확히 구글은 완전히 밖으로
bidding the highest bidder of any I I
모든 II의 최고 입찰자 입찰
understand that but I mean as we keep
이해하지만 우리는 계속 의미합니다
bumping these prices up people are gonna
사람들이이 가격을 부딪 히고
recognize oh if I find that one exploit
내가 하나의 익스플로잇을 발견하면 알아
it's gonna be a massive payday and I'm
엄청난 월급 날이되고 난
not happy with 1.5 like right now we're
우리는 지금처럼 1.5에 만족하지 않습니다
in 1.5 how long before we're gonna see a
1.5가 지나기 전에
three or a ten or a twenty five million
삼천 오백 오십 만
dollar payoff or an exploit to be
달러 지불 또는 악용
identified because I mean you have to
당신이해야한다는 것을 의미하기 때문에 식별
ask yourself how much money is Google
Google이 얼마나 많은 돈인지 스스로에게 물어보세요
gonna make in putting out these phones
이 전화를 넣어 만들거야
and you know is somebody gonna looking
그리고 당신은 누군가가 찾고있을 것이라는 것을 알고 있습니다
to be like yeah it's not good
그래 그래야 좋지 않아
like this does this just you know read
이처럼 당신이 읽는 것을 알고 있습니다.
some selfishness I don't know no I feel
내가 느끼지 못하는 이기심
like it's such a good pail like it's
그 것처럼 좋은 양동이처럼
such an amazing reward but I think that
정말 놀라운 보상이지만
people will actually up their game
사람들은 실제로 게임을
trying to find it turns into lecture it
그것을 찾으려고 노력하면 강의로 변합니다.
turns into trying to find an easter egg
부활절 달걀을 찾으려고 노력
in Oh some movie that I can't remember
내가 기억할 수없는 영화
right now there's Easter eggs in a whole
지금 당장 부활절 달걀이 있습니다
bunch of yes okay but it will make
그렇습니다.하지만 괜찮을 것입니다.
people try harder to actually find the
사람들은 실제로
exploit making the exploits obvious
악용을 명백하게하는 악용
faster making it more secure quicker and
더 빠르고 안전하게
then there won't be the option of
다음의 옵션이 없습니다
selling anything to the that they're I
그들이 나에게 무엇이든 판매
think that's the end because it's all
그것이 끝이기 때문에 그것이 끝이라고 생각
right so nobody's gonna be like can I
그래서 난 아무도 될 수 없어
have 751 if there's anything that we
우리가 가진 것이 있다면 751이 있습니다
know like from the whole marketplace of
전체 시장에서 같은 것을 알고
let's say ransomware just using the
랜섬웨어를 사용하여
example what do we know about hackers
우리는 해커에 대해 무엇을 알고 있습니까?
due to ransomware they want a quick
랜섬웨어로 인해 그들은 빠른 것을 원합니다
payday right so if I'm a hacker and I'm
내가 해커이고 나는
not but if I was and I found this
내가 아니라면 내가 이것을 찾았다면
exploit and was able to create an
착취하고 만들 수 있었다
exploit for the pixel I'm going to want
내가 원하는 픽셀을 악용
what a quick payday so am I gonna go to
얼마나 빠른 월급 날 이니
the guys that are giving me $100,000 or
나에게 $ 100,000를주는 사람들
am I gonna go to the ones that are
나는 그들에게 갈거야
paying me seven hundred and fifty
나에게 칠백 오십을 지불
thousand dollars you know what the
천 달러 당신은 무엇을 알고
answer to that is that is the idea
그것에 대한 답은 그 아이디어입니다
behind what Google is doing I suspect
구글이하고있는 일 뒤에
and I think that it's a really good
정말 좋은 것 같아요
motivator for for I'll say a motivator a
동기 부여를위한 동기 부여
lot of times what we perceive as a bad
우리가 나쁜 것으로 인식하는 많은 시간
guy in the hacking industry we'll call
해킹 산업에 종사하는 사람
it is really just somebody that it has
그것은 정말 누군가가
fallen upon the wrong channel okay if I
내가 틀렸다면 잘못된 채널에 떨어 졌어
find this hack oh I can sell it for a
이 핵을 찾으십시오.
hundred thousand dollars so if that's my
십만 달러이므로
option now I've got this opportunity to
옵션 지금 나는이 기회를 얻었다
get a hundred thousand dollars right and
십만 달러를 받고
it's not necessarily that they are a bad
반드시 그들이 나쁜 것은 아닙니다
person or that they are doing a bad
사람 또는 그들이 나쁜 짓을하고 있음
thing is just well but now it's been
일이 잘되었지만 지금은
weaponized because the the that group
그 그룹 때문에 무기
has bought it so what they're doing is
그들이하던 일을 샀습니다
they're also reallocating the
그들은 또한 재 할당하고 있습니다
the brilliant minds of the youth and the
젊음의 훌륭한 마음과
the hacker the hackers and RIA
해커 해커와 RIA
redirecting that toward correcting the
그 방향으로 수정
situation and saying okay we'll give you
상황과 괜찮다고 우리는 당신에게 줄 것이다
more money and and you're gonna you're
더 많은 돈과 당신은 당신이거야
helping to improve the security of the
의 보안을 향상시키는 데 도움
platform right so I think it's a whole
플랫폼이라고 생각합니다.
it does so much good I agree
동의합니다
I think they should also offer them a
나는 그들이 또한 그들에게 제공해야한다고 생각
job to be honest and that that could
정직한 직업과
happen yeah Microsoft used to do that
그래, 마이크로 소프트가 그렇게 했었지
years ago when they first set up their
몇 년 전 그들이 처음 설정했을 때
website it was it can happen multiple
웹 사이트 그것은 여러 번 일어날 수 있었다
layers of security like if you break in
침입 할 경우와 같은 보안 계층
you get a job here I feel like this
당신은 여기에 직업을 얻는다
whole story is something that like would
전체 이야기는
inspire Amy didi right like sure just be
에이미 디디에게 영감을주는 것
like yeah I'm all over this we've got to
그래, 난 우리가해야 할 일이 끝났어
take a quick break the crypto report and
암호화 보고서를 빠르게 중단하고
more of this week's top tech stories are
이번 주 최고의 기술 스토리는
coming up don't go anywhere
아무데도 가지마
[Music]
[음악]
you
당신
welcome
환영
a quick look at the crypto report and
암호화 보고서를 간략히 살펴보고
how things look as of Wednesday November
11 월 수요일 현재의 모습
27th 2019 via our website category 5 dot
우리의 웹 사이트 카테고리 5를 통해 2019 년 27 일
TV we've been collecting the data and
우리는 데이터를 수집하고 TV
looking at how things have been
상황이 어땠는지보고
transitioning over the past week and
지난 주에 전환
we're seeing the Bitcoin is really
우리는 비트 코인이
losing a fair bit this week dropping
이번 주에 조금 떨어졌다
down more than a thousand dollars u.s.
천 달러 이상 우리
as far as its US dollar equivalent value
미국 달러 상당의 가치
down at seven thousand one hundred and
칠천 칠백으로
ninety three dollars and change
구 십오 달러와 변화
litecoin is also down I mean everything
litecoin도 다운되었습니다 모든 것을 의미합니다
is on is on the decline this week it's
이 주에 감소에있다
at forty six dollars and 87 cents
마흔 육십 육 달러와 87 센트
aetherium is at one forty seven eighty
aetherium의 나이는 197입니다.
one Manero is down at fifty one fifty
하나의 Manero는 50에서 50
four not dropping as much as I would
내가 원하는만큼 떨어지지 않습니다
have expected considering the exploit
악용을 고려하여 예상
that happened on their website this week
이번 주에 웹 사이트에서 발생한
turtle coin is holding fairly steady
거북이 동전은 상당히 안정적입니다
having dropped just zero point zero one
영점 0 만 떨어 뜨림
ten thousandth of ascent to zero point
영점에서 천만 상승
two three and we're now looking at the
둘 셋 그리고 우리는 지금보고
basic attention token as well and that
기본주의 토큰과
is down from last week at zero
지난 주에 0으로 다운되었습니다
well 21 cents US per coin remember that
동전 당 21 센트의 미국이
this is not we're not providing any kind
이것은 우리가 어떤 종류도 제공하지 않습니다
of financial advice or investment advice
재정 조언 또는 투자 조언
what we are giving you is just the facts
우리가 당신에게주는 것은 단지 사실입니다
with regards to cryptocurrency and the
암호 화폐와 관련하여
different coins that we are monitoring
우리가 모니터링하는 다른 동전
here at the studio the cryptocurrency
여기 스튜디오에서 cryptocurrency
market never closes
시장은 절대 닫히지 않는다
and it's always volatile so make sure
항상 휘발성이므로
that you only invest what you are able
당신이 할 수있는 것만 투자한다는
and willing to lose because it's quite
상당히 기꺼이 잃을 의지
probable that you may never turn in an
당신은 결코 켜지지 않을 것입니다
income from it and that's not our intent
그것의 수입은 우리의 의도가 아닙니다
we just want to give you the facts you
우리는 단지 당신에게 당신에게 사실을주고 싶어
can find out more at category-five dot
카테고리 5 도트에서 더 많은 것을 찾을 수 있습니다
TV click on shows the category-five TV
TV를 클릭하면 카테고리 5 TV가 표시됩니다.
newsroom and you'll see the crypto
뉴스 룸과 암호를 볼 수 있습니다
report there and that will just give you
거기에보고하면 그것은 당신에게 줄 것입니다.
up to up to the day cryptocurrency data
cryptocurrency 데이터까지
for the coins that we are tracking I'm
우리가 추적하는 동전을 위해
gonna head back over the newsroom to you
뉴스 룸으로 돌아가서
two
두
Thank You Ravi the official site for the
감사합니다 라비의 공식 사이트
Monaro digital coin was hacked to
Monaro 디지털 코인이 해킹당했습니다.
deliver currency stealing malware to you
화폐 도용 맬웨어를 귀하에게 제공
speaking of we're downloading a wallet
우리가 지갑을 다운로드한다고
software mm-hmm yep
소프트웨어 mm-hmm yep
the supply-chain attack came to light
공급망 공격이 가벼워졌다
last week Monday when a
지난 주 월요일
user reported that the cryptographic
사용자는 암호화가
hash for a command line interface wallet
커맨드 라인 인터페이스 지갑의 해시
downloaded from the site didn't match
사이트에서 다운로드 한 내용이 일치하지 않습니다
the hash listed on the page over the
페이지에 나열된 해시
next several hours users discovered that
다음 몇 시간 동안 사용자는
the mismatching hash wasn't the result
일치하지 않는 해시는 결과가 아닙니다
of an error instead it was an attack
대신 오류의 공격
designed to infect get Manero users with
Manero 사용자를 감염 시키도록 설계
malware site officials later confirmed
멀웨어 사이트 관리는 나중에 확인
that finding an analysis of the
그 분석을 찾는
malicious Linux binary found that it
악성 리눅스 바이너리는
added a few new functions to the
몇 가지 새로운 기능을 추가
legitimate one one of the functions was
합법적 인 기능 중 하나는
called after user opened or created a
사용자가 열거 나 생성 한 후 호출
new wallet it sent the wallet seed which
새 지갑은 지갑 씨앗을 보냈습니다.
is the cryptographic secret key used to
암호 비밀 키는
access wallet funds to a third party
제 3 자에게 지갑 자금에 액세스
server the malware then sent wallet
서버는 맬웨어가 지갑을 보냈다
funds to another server at least one
적어도 하나의 다른 서버에 자금
person participating in a reddit forum
레딧 포럼에 참여하는 사람
claimed to have lost digital coins after
이후 디지털 동전을 잃어 버렸다고 주장
installing the malicious Linux binary a
악성 리눅스 바이너리 설치
malicious Windows version of the CLI
CLI의 악성 Windows 버전
wallet carried out an almost identical
지갑은 거의 동일하게 수행
attack sequence anyone who downloaded
다운로드 한 사람의 공격 순서
the CLI Manero wallet on Monday November
11 월 월요일에 CLI Manero 지갑
2019 is advised to check the hashes of
2019는 해시를 확인하는 것이 좋습니다
their binaries if they don't match the
그들이 일치하지 않으면 그들의 바이너리
official ones delete the files and
공식적인 파일을 삭제하고
download them again do not run
다시 다운로드하지 마십시오.
compromised binaries for any reason I
어떤 이유로 든 손상된 바이너리
think yeah and this just goes to show
그래, 이건 그냥 보여
like if there is a checksum difference
체크섬 차이가있는 경우처럼
so if you've got the md5 or the sha
md5 또는 sha가 있다면
checksum and it doesn't match what it's
체크섬과 일치하지 않습니다
supposed to be just don't even touch it
손대지 마
just like find out what's going on
무슨 일인지 알아내는 것처럼
because you may think hey well that
당신이 잘 생각할 수 있기 때문에
that's weird it doesn't match well in
이상하게 일치하지 않습니다.
this particular case it could have saved
이 특별한 경우는
like the one that I heard of like lost
내가 잃어버린 것처럼 들었던
$7,000 out of their wallet as far as US
미국까지는 지갑에서 $ 7,000
currency goes and it just you know you
통화가 가고 당신은 당신을 알고 있습니다
got to be careful and crypto currency is
조심해야하고 암호화 통화는
a really really lucrative target for
정말 유리한 목표
malicious attackers and it can happen it
악의적 인 공격자 일 수 있으며
can happen and in this case hey you have
일어날 수 있고이 경우에 당신은 가지고 있습니다
to be really diligent
정말 부지런하다
I mean it would be it would be so simple
너무 간단 할 것 같아요
just to assume that everything was going
모든 것이 진행되고 있다고 가정
right except here here you go and the
바로 여기를 제외하고는
hashes don't match oh yeah well exactly
해시는 일치하지 않습니다.
and I mean I know that there's different
나는 다른 것을 알고
type of wallets you can use like you can
당신이 할 수있는 것처럼 사용할 수있는 지갑 유형
use your cloud-based wallet you can have
클라우드 기반 지갑을 사용할 수 있습니다
a software wallet you can have a paper
종이를 가질 수있는 소프트웨어 지갑
wallet that's completely cut off from
완전히 끊어진 지갑
the world
세계
but I mean each of them comes with their
그러나 나는 그들 각각이 그들의
own risks I mean and if you're gonna go
자신의 위험을 의미하고 당신이 갈 경우
with a paper wallet cuz you're like hey
종이 지갑으로 당신은 이봐 요
I don't want to be caught by something
뭔가에 걸리고 싶지 않아
like this if you ever lose your paper
종이를 잃어버린 경우
you're toast right you know and it's
당신은 당신이 알고 바로 토스트있어
unfortunate I mean as somebody who is
불행히도 나는 누군가 인 것을 의미합니다
mined monaro in the past you know it's
과거에 채굴 된 모나로
so easy to just kind of like oh here's
오 여기처럼
you know another wall I'm gonna try this
당신은 내가 시도 할 다른 벽을 알고
sure and you're not even paying
물론 당신은 지불하지 않습니다
attention and then you hit your miner
관심과 광부를 명중
and away you go
그리고 당신은 멀리 이동
you know and you walk away and then
당신은 알고 당신은 멀리 걸어
comeback days later to see how you're
며칠 후 돌아와서 어떻게 지내고 있는지
doing and in that meantime you've lost
그리고 그 동안 당신은 잃어버린
everything because you're not paying
당신이 지불하지 않기 때문에 모든 것
attention and it's so easy to do Jeff
주의하고 너무 쉽게 제프
I've even heard of people that will set
나는 설정할 사람들에 대해 들었습니다.
up automatic updates for their wallet
지갑 자동 업데이트
software and their mining software and
소프트웨어 및 마이닝 소프트웨어
when you do that and it's it's tough
당신이 그렇게 할 때 그것은 힘든
because a lot of times like scale is a
스케일과 같은 많은 시간이
perfect example where the coin has
동전이있는 완벽한 예
changed so many times that it just gets
너무 많은 시간을 변경하여
frustrating because you've got to keep
당신이 유지해야하기 때문에 좌절
reinstalling the software so people will
사람들이 소프트웨어를 다시 설치
tend to set up an automatic updater and
자동 업데이터를 설정하는 경향이 있으며
what happens if that update comes down
해당 업데이트가 중단되면 어떻게됩니까
the wire and it's malicious that's a big
와이어와 큰 악성
problem and when it comes to
문제와 관련하여
cryptocurrency
암호 화폐
there's there's really no way to get
얻을 수있는 방법이 정말 없습니다
your money back was gone it's no it's
네 돈은 없어졌어 아니야
not like it's a regulated financial
규제 된 금융이 아닌 것
transaction where you know you can buy
구매할 수있는 거래
insurance on it right it's not insured
보험에 가입하지 않았습니다.
in any way it's scary that this is
어쨌든 이것이 무섭습니다.
happening so I feel like early in the
그래서 나는 일찍 느끼고
life of cryptocurrency but I know it's
cryptocurrency의 삶이지만 나는 그것이
not like early early days but I feel
초기 초기는 아니지만 느낌이 듭니다
like it's scary that now as it's
지금처럼 무서운 것처럼
becoming more common knowledge that
더 일반적인 지식이되고
cryptocurrency exists and people are
암호 화폐가 존재하고 사람들은
kind of getting right on the bandwagon
악 대차에 타는 종류
in the malls there are Bitcoin vendors
쇼핑몰에는 Bitcoin 공급 업체가 있습니다
and now this is coming out which makes
그리고 지금 이것은 나오는
me think is this the beginning of a
나는 이것이 시작의 생각
cycle that's going to gain momentum
운동량을 얻을 사이클
and I wonder whether there is going to
그리고 나는 갈 것인지 궁금해
be a way then to ensure that that's a
그런 다음 그 방법을
valid concern Sasha yeah but I think
유효한 관심사 Sasha 그래
what it is is it's really just like this
이게 진짜 이렇습니다
is something that's gonna constantly be
끊임없이 될 것입니다
under attack so is this gonna be a wake
공격을 받고 있으므로 이것은 깨어날 것입니다
up call Foreman arrows developers for
Foreman 화살표 개발자를 불러
example to solidify their security
보안을 강화하는 예
something went wrong
무언가 잘못되었다
something allowed this to happen they'll
그들이 일어날 수있는 무언가
need to figure out what happened and put
무슨 일이 있었는지 알아 내고 넣어
a stop to it and and protect their users
중지하고 사용자를 보호
plain and simple it makes me wonder I
평범하고 단순해서 내가 궁금해합니다
mean because you already have the US
이미 미국을 가지고 있기 때문에 의미
government looking at regulatory
정부 규제보고
oversight and declaring libre from
감시 및 리브레 선언
Facebook
페이스 북
right as securities currency it makes me
증권 통화로
wonder if this is gonna open the door
이것이 문을 열지 궁금해
because the issues we've that have gone
우리가 겪은 문제는
around the globe with Bitcoin and now
비트 코인으로 전 세계에
you've got this issue with monaro if
monaro 에이 문제가 있습니다.
it's gonna start pushing regulatory
규제를 추진하기 시작합니다
oversight in legislation that says you
입법에 대한 감독
know what cryptocurrencies are in fact a
실제로 cryptocurrencies가 무엇인지 알고
financial transaction they should be
그들이해야하는 금융 거래
governed by the navvies Commission I
해군위원회 I의 지배
don't fear that no but it makes you it
그것을 두려워하지 마십시오. 그러나 그것은 당신을 만듭니다.
does make me wonder if it's gonna get to
내가 갈 수 있는지 궁금해하지 않습니다
the point where somebody's gonna bring
누군가가 가져올 지점
that topic up and say this needs to
그 주제를 말하고 이것이 필요하다고 말하십시오.
happen now they're just gonna say too
이제 그들은 단지 너무 말할거야
bad so sad it's not a valid currency
너무 슬프다 그것은 유효한 통화가 아니다
that's how they'll move on yeah and
그것이 그들이 어떻게 움직일 것인가입니다.
speaking of Sasha we're gonna jump into
사샤에 대해 이야기하면
the next story wouldn't it be nice if
다음 이야기는 좋지 않을 것입니다
there was a facebook rival well there is
페이 스북 라이벌이 잘 있었다
and it's founded by the guy who built
그리고 그것은 만든 사람에 의해 설립
Wikipedia Jimmy Wales is expressing
지미 웨일즈
excitement that his new social network
그의 새로운 소셜 네트워크를 흥분
WT social already has more than 160,000
WT 사회는 이미 160,000 이상을 가지고 있습니다
members the platform says it will never
회원 플랫폼은 결코하지 않을 것이라고 말합니다
sell user data and relies on the
사용자 데이터를 판매하고
generosity of individual donors rather
오히려 개별 기증자의 관대함
than ads the donations are by way of a
기부금은 광고보다
modest subscription fee it is
적당한 가입비
positioning itself as news focused place
뉴스 중심 장소로 자리 매김
and says members will be able to edit
회원들이 편집 할 수 있다고 말합니다
misleading headlines they will see the
오해의 소지가있는 헤드 라인
articles shared by their network in a
네트워크에서 공유 한 기사
timeline format appearing with the
와 함께 나타나는 타임 라인 형식
newest first rather than algorithms that
알고리즘보다는 최신의
try to appeal to their interests the
그들의 관심사에 호소하려고
introduction to WT social says quote we
WT 소셜 소개는 우리가 견적을 말한다
will empower you to make your own
당신이 당신의 자신을 만들 힘을 줄 것입니다
choices about
에 대한 선택
content you are served and to directly
귀하가 직접 제공하는 콘텐츠
edit misleading headlines or flag
잘못된 헤드 라인 또는 플래그 수정
problem posts we will foster an
우리는 문제 게시물을 육성
environment where bad actors are removed
나쁜 행위자가 제거되는 환경
because it is right not because it
그것이 아니기 때문에 옳기 때문에
suddenly affects our bottom line unquote
갑자기 우리의 결론에 영향을 미칩니다
in a recent interview with the Financial
최근 파이낸셜과의 인터뷰에서
Times mr. Wales shared his view that the
타임즈 씨 웨일즈는
problem with advertising LED services
광고 LED 서비스 문제
such as Facebook is that the winners
페이스 북과 같은 승자가
often low-quality content social media
종종 저품질 콘텐츠 소셜 미디어
consultant consultant Zoe Carnes said
컨설턴트 컨설턴트 조 카네 스는 말했다
that she thought the network would have
그녀는 네트워크가 가질 것이라고 생각
to grow its numbers quickly in order to
빠르게 숫자를 키우고
prove itself to be an a viable
그 자체가 실행 가능한 것으로 증명
alternative to the Giants she says quote
자이언츠에 대한 대안
it's going to need a lot of money plowed
많은 돈이 필요합니다
into it people are so used to social
그것에 사람들은 너무 사회에 익숙해
media being free I think businesses
언론은 자유 롭다
might pay for it but people are so used
돈을 지불 할 수도 있지만 사람들은 너무 많이 사용됩니다
to having news at their fingertips for
그들의 손끝에 뉴스를 갖는
free and quote WT social is a separate
무료 및 견적 WT 사회는 별도입니다
entity to Wikipedia and can be found at
Wikipedia에 대한 엔티티이며
WT dot social this is an interesting one
WT 도트 사회 이것은 흥미로운 것입니다
I would say that this is not necessarily
나는 이것이 반드시 그런 것은 아니라고 말할 것입니다
something that I'm going to immediately
내가 곧 갈 것
delve into but I like the idea of paying
탐구하지만 나는 지불의 아이디어를 좋아한다
for the idea that my stuff is never
내 물건이 결코 없다는 아이디어
gonna be sold like if I think you're not
내가 아닌 것 같아서 팔릴거야
going to be from the sound of it you're
너의 소리에서 나올거야.
not going to be manipulated right by
에 의해 바로 조작되지 않을 것
what is making them money exactly now
그들이 지금 정확히 돈을 버는 것
the tricky part about it is a little bit
그것에 대한 까다로운 부분은 약간입니다
like in the back of my mind I think
내 생각처럼
Wikipedia isn't like a super reliable
Wikipedia는 믿을만한 것이 아닙니다
source when you're doing research but
당신이 연구를 할 때 소스하지만
this isn't about research this is about
이것은 연구에 관한 것이 아닙니다.
entertaining news stories social media
재미있는 뉴스 이야기 소셜 미디어
yeah see I wonder though like I get what
그래, 내가 무엇을 얻는 것처럼 궁금해 참조
they're going for and and I get the
그들은 가고 있고 나는
whole subscription-based thing whatever
구독 기반의 모든 것
that modest fee might be I don't know if
그 겸손한 수수료는 내가 모른다면
it's something I will but would you pay
그것은 내가 할 것이지만 당신은 지불 할 것입니다
fourteen now see I don't think I would
14 명은 이제 내가 생각하지 않을 것입니다 참조
because once they get you hooked then
일단 그들이 당신을 사로 잡으면
the fees go up because oh it's more
오 더 많아서 수수료가 올라간다
expensive we've got it Wow Jeff is like
비싸다 우와 제프는
all over like as soon as you give them
당신이 그들에게주는 즉시 온통
five dollars it'll be ten dollars time
5 달러는 10 달러입니다
okay that's the way that Netflix was and
네, 넷플릭스의 방식이었고
I mean as they keep pushing on new
그들이 새로운 것을 계속 추진하면서
content which I I'm not knocking Netflix
내가 Netflix를 노크하지 않는 콘텐츠
but I mean you get locked in at 7:19
하지만 난 당신이 7시 19 분에 갇혀 의미
what was a ten years ago and now you're
10 년 전과 지금은
looking at 1499 like the price is
가격처럼 1499를 보면
doubled and you're still getting the
두 배로되며 여전히
same services just extra content they're
동일한 서비스 만 추가 콘텐츠
producing more show but I mean that's
더 많은 쇼를 제작하지만
Netflix the whole point with this thing
넷플릭스 이것으로 요점
my concern though is the fact that it's
그래도 내 관심사는
user edited input like we already have a
우리가 이미 가지고있는 것처럼 사용자 편집 입력
problem now with fake news and milla
가짜 뉴스와 밀라의 문제
manipulated the opposite of fake news
가짜 뉴스의 반대를 조작
though I understand that but somebody
이해하지만 누군가
added I mean you see this now with
추가 나는 당신이 지금 이것을 참조 의미
Wikipedia I mean what was it about for
위키피디아
15 years there was a fake religious god
15 년 동안 가짜 종교 신이있었습니다
that was on Wikipedia that was deemed to
그건 Wikipedia에 있던 것으로
be real but in fact it wasn't because
사실이지만 실제로는 아니었기 때문에
somebody put something on there that
누군가가 거기에 뭔가를 넣어
wasn't true and it never got caught so
사실이 아니었고 그렇게 잡히지 않았습니다.
what's to say you have a news article
뉴스 기사가 있다고 할 말
where somebody goes hey you know what
누군가가가는 곳 당신은 무엇을 알고
this is this is a great article but I
이것은 좋은 기사이지만 나는
think I need to change it just just
그냥 바꾸어야한다고 생각합니다
slightly so that it's 98% true but
98 %가되도록 약간
there's a little bit of false fact in it
거기에 약간의 잘못된 사실이 있습니다.
and suddenly it continues to grow and it
갑자기 계속 자랍니다
takes off we already have this problem
이 문제는 이미 해결되었습니다
now the whole idea of having a social
이제 사회를 갖는 모든 아이디어
medias subscription-based service that
미디어 구독 기반 서비스
people can then edit and alter the news
사람들은 뉴스를 편집하고 변경할 수 있습니다
on I find wrong but the alternative is a
나는 잘못 찾았지만 대안은
social media platform where you don't
당신이하지 않는 소셜 미디어 플랫폼
have the opportunity to edit those who
그 사람들을 편집 할 수있는 기회를
have the money control exactly those who
돈을 정확하게 제어하는 ​​사람
have who put billions of dollars into it
수십억 달러를 넣은 사람
are able to control and edit so if
제어하고 편집 할 수 있다면
you're given the choice of only two
당신은 두 가지 중에서 선택할 수 있습니다
things you're given Facebook or WT
Facebook 또는 WT에 제공되는 것들
social Facebook is free but right but
소셜 Facebook은 무료이지만 옳지 만
you're going to be manipulated according
당신은 따라 조작 될거야
to what they think you want to see
그들이 당신이보고 싶어하는 것에
social is going to show you news stories
사회는 당신에게 뉴스 기사를 보여줄 것입니다
that could perhaps be edited by peers so
그것은 아마도 동료에 의해 편집 될 수 있습니다
the question becomes then Jeff would you
질문은 제프가 될 것입니다
give WT social a chance by trying it for
WT 소셜에 도전하여 기회를주세요
a couple of months just to see if your
몇 달 동안
concerns are valid or are you so dead
우려가 유효하거나 너무 죽었습니까
set against this kind of idea I mean I
이런 종류의 생각에 맞서는
love the idea of Wikipedia I love that
Wikipedia의 아이디어를 사랑합니다.
social aspect of sharing and Fries I do
공유와 감자 튀김의 사회적 측면
too and I and I use
나도 사용하고
Media often I would be willing to give
미디어는 종종 기꺼이 줄 것입니다
WT social a try not interested in paying
WT 소셜 지불에 관심이없는 시도
for it yeah like if they want to get
그들이 원하는 경우에 그래
people on board they need to open up the
사람들은 보드를 열어야합니다
doors for say three or six months get
3 개월에서 6 개월 동안
people sucked in where it's free they
사람들은 무료로 빨려 들어갔습니다
start building a presence there because
거기에 존재를 구축하기 시작
so many people I think are gonna turn an
너무 많은 사람들이
eye to this and go I'm not putting up
이것에 눈을 감고 가지 않고 있어요
many money for something where there's
있는 곳에 많은 돈
only 160,000 people I have to just say
그냥 160,000 명만 말하면됩니다
that actually nothing is free no it's
실제로 아무것도 무료가 아닙니다.
true that I I understand that right way
II는 올바른 방법을 이해한다는 사실
or another you're paying for it so I
또는 다른 하나는 당신이 그것을 지불하고 그래서
would rather actually pay money out of
오히려 실제로 돈을 지불
my pocket than to try and be afraid of
시도하고 두려워하는 것보다 내 주머니
where they're making money on my behalf
그들이 나를 위해 돈을 버는 곳
like where where are they getting the
그들이 어디로 가는지
money from me existing like but there's
나에게서 돈은 같은 존재하지만
on that but there's no way that you're
그것에 있지만 당신이있는 방법은 없습니다
gonna be able to say that the data and
데이터를 말할 수 있고
how you use their site still isn't going
당신은 그들의 사이트를 사용하는 방법은 여전히 ​​간다
to be used for somebody's personal game
누군가의 개인 게임에 사용
they said they're not going to sell it
그들은 그것을 팔지 않을 것이라고 말했다
it doesn't mean the fact that they can't
그들이 할 수 없다는 사실을 의미하지는 않습니다
have subsidiary companies that utilize
자회사를 활용하다
that same information or really Jeff
같은 정보 또는 정말 Jeff
we're getting into speculative this is
우리는 추측으로 들어가고 있습니다.
all speculation and I don't like to go
모든 추측과 나는 가고 싶지 않아
there and I actually love the idea that
저와 저는 실제로
somebody any somebody's got to do
누군가 누군가해야 할 일
something different is coming up and
다른 무언가가오고있다
saying hey you're not stuck with the one
이봐, 당신은 하나에 붙어 있지 않습니다
choice there is now going to be other
선택은 이제 다른 것입니다
choices and maybe this isn't the only
선택과 어쩌면 이것이 유일한 것은 아닙니다
one that's gonna exist this is the first
존재하는 것은 이것이 첫 번째입니다
of maybe many I agree that there's
아마도 많은 사람들이
always going to be changing options I
항상 옵션을 바꿀 것입니다.
just there's something about it just
그것에 대해 뭔가가 있습니다.
kind of thanks to Roy W Nash and our
Roy W Nash와
community of viewers for submitting
제출을위한 시청자 커뮤니티
stories to us this week thanks for
이번 주 우리에게 이야기
watching the category-five TV newsroom
카테고리 5 TV 뉴스 룸 시청
don't forget to Like and subscribe for
좋아하고 구독하는 것을 잊지 마세요
all your tech news with a slight lytx
약간의 lytx로 모든 기술 뉴스
bias and if you appreciate what we do
편견과 우리가하는 일에 감사한다면
become a patron at e3 on.com slash
e3 on.com 슬래시에서 후원자가 되십시오
newsroom
뉴스 편집실
from the category 5 TV newsroom and sash
카테고리 5 TV 뉴스 룸 및 새시
your estimate I'm Robbie Ferguson and
당신의 견적은 로비 퍼거슨이고
I'm Jeff Lester we've been to take a
제프 레스터입니다.
really quick break folks stick around
정말 빠른 휴식 사람들이 붙어
[Music]
[음악]
well thank you so much for joining us
우리와 함께 해주셔서 감사합니다
this week everybody it's been a blast it
이번 주에 여러분 모두는 폭발했습니다
is time for us to add more space to our
우리 공간을 더 늘릴 시간입니다
storage server and here at the studio of
스토리지 서버와 여기 스튜디오에서
course we produce HD and now ultra HD
물론 우리는 HD를 생산하고 이제는 울트라 HD
video every single week and we've been
매주 비디오 및 우리는
doing so now we're in our 13th season of
지금 우리는 13 번째 시즌에 있습니다.
doing so every single week and that
매주 그렇게하고
takes up a lot of space but the question
많은 공간을 차지하지만 문제는
now becomes do we add more spinning
이제 우리는 더 많은 회전을 추가합니까
discs to our storage server as we've
스토리지 서버에 디스크를
always done or is it time to switch to
항상 완료 했습니까?
SSDs and then we say well is it really
SSD와 우리는 잘 말합니다
worth going to SSDs and I'm talking
SSD에 갈 가치가 있고 이야기하고 있습니다.
enterprise level Kingston SSDs is it
엔터프라이즈 급 Kingston SSD
gonna be worth it and so we're actually
그럴만 한 가치가 있고 실제로 우리는
going to put it to the test we're gonna
우리가 할 테스트에 넣을 것입니다
look at the thermals we're gonna look at
우리가 보려고하는 열을 보아라
the speed we're gonna look at how well
우리가 볼 속도는
they perform in as a replacement storage
그들은 대체 스토리지로 수행
device so pulling out the old spinning
오래된 회전을 당기는 장치
drives and putting in some new SSDs
드라이브 및 새로운 SSD 장착
let's see how things are gonna change so
상황이 어떻게 변하는 지 보자
that's all happening next week I hope
그 다음 주에 모든 일이 일어나길 바랍니다.
that you'll be able to join us thank you
당신이 우리와 함께 할 수있을 것입니다 감사합니다
so much again for being here with us
우리와 함께 여기에 다시 너무 많이
this week I'm Robbie Ferguson say and
이번 주 저는 로비 퍼거슨이라고합니다
have a great night and you too over
좋은 밤 되세요 너도 끝났어
there see everybody
모두를 참조하십시오
[Music]
[음악]